I have an idea!
If Agent Alex wants to stay here with us,
then she should be willing to put up with
whatever she ends up hearing.
Luisa Mae is Laurence's girlfriend?
You're a couple!
No, we actually have more
of a connection with Angelito.
Because between two women, Alex,
Mikoy loves watching soap operas.
Even I'm starting to enjoy them.
But what I don't like is,
they always throw in a third party.
But I can't really blame you.
It's not hard to like Mikoy.
Actually, he's easy to love.
But right now,
it doesn't matter anymore.
It doesn't matter who
or how many people have fallen for him.
What's important is,
Mikoy chose me…
and I'm the one he loves.
Then in that case,
you have nothing to worry about.
Why did you suddenly go quiet?
Did we interrupt something?
Looks like you were gossiping about us.
Sweetheart, we were just talking about
how lovable you are,
and how you make this stay less boring.
I thought it was something serious.
And of course,
everybody loves me.
I'm the life of the party, you know.
Of course!
There we go!
So my kiss passed the test?
Looks like I'll make it into
the top three next time.
Oh, here.
Hey.
Why, bro?
While they're busy,
there's something I want to tell you.
Not now. I still have a lot
to clean up from the tortilla stand.
This will be quick, I promise.
I really just need your help.
Help?
-Why me?
-You're friends with Sofie, right?
Is this about
what you told her earlier?
That you want her to say yes?
Yes.
Angelito. I want to court Sofie.
Can you help me?
Come on.
Okay.
Thank you.
Bestfriend.
I really can't take it anymore.
So noisy.
The scenery is actually nice at night.
You can clearly see the stars.
Unlike in the city.
What are you doing, sweetheart?
I'm catching a star.
I want to make a wish.
Let me help you
so you can make more wishes.
There.
Here, this one's cute.
Wow! There are so many!
There!
So you can make more wishes.
Right?
What do you wish for?
My wish is,
that the two of us will finally be free.
No agency.
No Concordat.
No safehouse.
No safehouse mates.
Just the two of us.
In our own world.
Good thing I already got my star.
Oh, please!
That's so cheesy.
Admit it, you got butterflies.
When did you realize you liked Sofie?
It's more than just liking her.
It's like…
Like what?
Like I love her.
That fast?
You already love her?
Are you even close?
I mean,
haven't you only spent
a little time together?
You know, Angelito,
I've always believed that
it's not really about how long
you've known someone
to love them.
And I admit
that Sofie and I have only
spent a little time together.
But honestly,
I feel sad when she's sad.
I do everything I can to make her happy.
Now tell me,
if this isn't love,
then what is it? Madness?
I don't know either.
But wait, what kind of
help do you want from me exactly?
Just kidding. Seriously though.
Me too.
Of course I miss that too.
Just the two of us.
Away from all the noise of the world.
But you know,
maybe this is actually
a good opportunity for us.
Because we can't spend
our whole lives running.
Right?
Like you said,
we have families,
friends,
people who love us,
and we can't turn our backs on them.
Maybe,
this,
us staying here,
might be the first step toward
returning to them someday.
And don't think
that's no longer what I want.
Of course I love being alone with you.
Of course.
If it were up to me,
we'd stay hidden forever.
But…
But sooner or later,
we have to face the music of life.
Are you serious?
Just remember this.
In the darkness,
the stars shine even brighter.
You know, Angelito,
I'm aware that
you and Sofie
have a weird friendship, right?
You've told me all about it.
And more importantly,
you probably know that
I don't want to be a jerk of a friend.
Because the bro code is important to me.
Now let me ask you.
Are you and Sofie just friends?
Of course.
We're just friends.
You don't listen to my rants, do you?
-Really?
-Yes.
It's probably not too late
to confess, right?
That's right. We're just friends.
Especially after we found out that
our parents were actually
friends too, a long time ago.
Since they were kids.
-Really?
-Exactly!
You know Sofie,
she's practically my sister.
Really?
Yes.
Here. Mama Tess sent this over,
so you'd have something to go with
the drink you're having.
Thank you, Sofie.
Would you like to sit down first?
No, I still have something to do upstairs.
And what's on her mind again?
The sunlight is perfect,
so forget what you saw last night.
Don't let it affect you.
You're here for the mission.
You are disciplined.
It's just a feeling,
you are Special Agent Alex.
Remember, Alex, you can't lose any fight.
Let's not get out of bed.
Is that okay?
Is that the boneless one? Just kidding.
-Is it seedless? Seedless?
-Yes, ma'am.
Are you sure? Because what if…
What is this? Why is…
Why is Aquaman here too?
You've turned my house into
some kind of co-working space.
Have you found the two of them yet?
Not yet, Ma'am.
But we've already sent people to the place
where we suspect they're hiding.
Good.
Report to me once you find them.
Where are you Chiara?
I would just like to remind you
that you need to update ASAP.
Because Senator Quintin will have a
briefing with our President.
Okay, I'll send it once I finish it.
Agent Alex, there's a problem!
What?
You're so annoying.
Do you like jelly beans?
I found it in the pantry.
Maybe you want some.
At this point, we still don't know why
La Morte Bianca is building the site.
We're not sure yet.
If you really want to know what they know,
we need to talk to one of their people.